Carl Oglesby Papers, 1942-2005
Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 3: Yankee and Cowboy War, 1970-2002
  In one of Oglesby's most widely known political theories, referred to as the "Yankee and Cowboy War," he depicts Northern, old money "Yankees" and Southern and Western, new money "Cowboys" in a struggle for power and dominance in post-World War II America. His book named for the theory traces the effects of this political struggle from the Bay of Pigs incident in 1961 to Watergate in 1973-1974.
  In the book, Oglesby claims that the failure of the Bay of Pigs Invasion was the result of internal conflict in Washington, namely the shaky coalition between President John F. Kennedy (Yankee) and Vice President Lyndon B. Johnson (Cowboy). Oglesby further claims that this uneasy alliance between the North and South resulted in the escalation of the Vietnam War, as well as other foreign policy disasters that plagued the administration before and after Kennedy's death. Oglesby refers to the Vietnam War as a "Cowboy War," which ultimately resulted in such high level pressure from "top class Yankee gunslingers," such as Defense Secretary Clark Clifford, that Johnson was unable to seek re-election. He also examines events such as the suspicious Watergate plane crash that killed Dorothy Hunt, the wife of Watergate conspirator E. Howard Hunt, the possibility that James McCord, also a Watergate conspirator, was a double agent, the assassination of John F. Kennedy, and Howard Hughes' relationship with the United States government.
  The series contains materials relating to Oglesby's book, such as drafts of the manuscript, research materials including articles and newspaper clippings, correspondence concerning its publication, and published reviews.
- Series 4: Gehlen Organization, 1945-2005
  For more than three decades, Oglesby researched the Gehlen Organization and its role in post-World War II America. As the war came to a close, top-ranking Nazi officials scrambled to find a way out of Germany. One such official was Reinhard Gehlen, the head of the Former Armies East (FHO) in the German Army Headquarters, also known as the Gehlen Organization. This was an important branch of the Nazi intelligence system that oversaw all intelligence and military operations throughout Eastern Europe and the Soviet Union. This arm of Soviet intelligence was particularly powerful because of Gehlen's close association with and influence over Foreign Armies West and the Odessa. The Odessa was arguably the Nazi's greatest organizational achievement because it not only controlled the SS and Gestapo but also set up "rat lines" which allowed thousands of Nazi officials to escape Germany after the war.
  The U.S. government, anxious to achieve a reliable intelligence network to spy on the Soviet Union, was not opposed to making a deal with Gehlen to acquire his West German intelligence network in exchange for allowing Nazis to quietly escape Germany after the war. The FHO, after all, was the only organization in the Third Reich that gained power and recruits even as the war was winding down. On August 24, 1945, one week after the Nazi's "unconditional surrender," Gehlen arrived in Washington D.C. to sell his organization to the United States and buy himself a way out of Germany.
  The meeting in Fort Hunt, Virgina, ended with a "gentleman's agreement" to employ Gehlen as an official in the newly formed C.I.A., for which Gehlen worked until 1968. Gehlen himself spelled out the terms of this agreement in his book, The Service: The Memoirs of Reinhard Gehlen, which has come under intense criticism for being inaccurate. Nonetheless, according to Gehlen, "The Secret Treaty at Fort Hunt" essentially merged Nazi Gehlen Organization and U.S. intelligence with the understanding that although the Germans and Americans would be working "jointly," the United States would provide complete funding for all activities. Interestingly, according to Gehlen, it was also understood that should German and American interests come into conflict with each other, the Gehlen Organization would "consider Germany first." This conflict of interest presented itself almost immediately as the post-war hunt for Nazi war criminals began and tensions between the Soviet Union and the United States escalated.
  Oglesby's interest in the Gehlen Organization ultimately resulted in a lawsuit against the federal government. In the suit (Carl Oglesby v. Department of the Army, et al), he claims the government refused to release documents that should be open to the public under the Freedom of Information Act. This lawsuit has been circulating through the court system for almost twenty years and has forced various governmental agencies to release thousands of pages of previously "classified" and "top secret" documents to Oglesby. Oglesby's counsel in this matter, James Lesar, specializes in litigation pertaining to the Freedom of Information Act, and has logged thousands of hours over the years fighting for the release of documents pertaining to World War II, the Gehlen Organization, and former Nazi government officials and military officers.
  Numerous drafts of articles, book excerpts and lectures are included in this series, although it should be noted that Oglesby has yet to publish a complete book on this topic. An extensive article by Oglesby, "The Secret Treaty of Fort Hunt," was published in Prevailing Winds magazine. A considerable portion of his research materials are also included in this series. These consist of articles, newspaper clippings, book excerpts, correspondence, charts drawn by Oglesby explaining the complicated connections between the various government agencies and people, government reports, and intelligence documents obtained by Lesar under the Freedom of Information Act.
- Series 5: Other Writings, 1959-2004
  - Ravens on the Wing, 1959-2003
    This subseries contains drafts and research material for Oglesby's memoir, "Ravens on the Wing." In it he covers, in detail, the move away from his middle class life as a technical copy editor in the defense industry, his experiences as president of SDS, which include his relationship with Weatherman founder Bernadine Dohrn, trips to Cuba and North Vietnam, and his travels around the country giving speeches for SDS. He also discusses the painful period when the Weatherman split from SDS and his own experiences with SDS after.
    Included in this subseries are numerous drafts of the memoir, published in 2008 as Ravens in the Storm. Also included is correspondence concerning the book, newspaper clippings, articles, writing fragments, notes, and some photographs from Oglesby's trip to Cuba.
  - Miscellaneous Writings and Research, 1961-2002
    This series, more than any other, chronicles Oglesby prodigious writing career. He has written extensively on SDS, the New Left, the JFK assassination, Vietnam, Watergate, and his theory of the Yankee-Cowboy war. Although the bulk of Oglesby's writing is political in nature, he has written about many things that range from discussions of the New Left, the war in Vietnam, critiques of teach-ins, literature, Cuba, Boston public transit, Boston University, genetic engineering, farms in America and many verses of unpublished poetry. Also included in this subseries is correspondence with people like Noam Chomsky, academic papers from Oglesby's undergraduate career and Oglesby's 1965 paper, "The Vietnam War: World Revolution and American Containment," which ultimately became the SDS position paper for the Vietnam War.
  - Religion, 1971-2004
    Although Oglesby has not written as extensively on religion, he has maintained his interest in it over the years, publishing two articles on the subject, "Rescuing Jesus from the Cross" (1983) and "Art at the Apocalypse" (1982). His unpublished manuscript "The Sermons of Judas" is also included along with research materials relating to this manuscript and other religious items such as church programs, flyers, and eulogies.
- Series 6: Personal, 1942-2003
  Oglesby's personal correspondence with various family members, business associates, and friends, as well as documents relating to his publishing contracts, photographs, announcements, invitations, and various printed materials and newspaper clippings. Also contains materials relating to Oglesby's work with the Center for Strategic and International Studies.
- Series 7: Audio-Visual, 1966-2000
  Both as president of SDS and later as a founder of the Assassination Information Bureau, Oglesby traveled around the country meeting people and giving talks. His 1966 lecture at Antioch College is included here as are the numerous slides he used when delivering his presentations on the assassination of Kennedy. Oglesby used audio and video recordings as part of his own research, compiling a collection of documentary's on the JFK assassination and Reinhard Gehlen and the Nazi connection to U.S. intelligence agencies.
- Series 1: Students for a Democratic Society (SDS), 1965-2005
  - Address list, undated (Box 1)
  - Articles: Dohrn, Bernadine, "The Split of the Weather Underground Organization", undated (Box 1)
  - Articles: Lind, Michael, "Vietnam, the Necessary War: A reinterpretation of America's Most Disastrous Conflict", 1999 (Box 1)
  - Articles: Oglesby, Carl, "The Death of SDS: Suicide or Murder?, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Articles: Radicalism in the United States, 2000-2003 (Box 1)
  - Articles: Shipler, David K., "Robert McNamera and the Ghost of Vietnam", 1997 (Box 1)
  - Articles: "Towards a History of the New Left", 1966 (Box 1)
  - Articles and books: Timberg, Robert, "The Nightingale's Song", 1995 (Box 1)
  - Articles and newspaper clippings: Dohrn, Bernadine, 1985-1999 (Box 1)
  - Articles and writings: FBI repression of the New Left, 1973-1974, undated (Box 1)
  - CIA files: SDS activities, 1973-1979 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1979, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence: Intelligence Documentation Center, 1976 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence: Lesar, Jim, 2002-2005 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence: U.S. Government, 1974-1976 (Box 1)
  - Court documents: Carl Oglesby v. Department of Justice, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Essay: Simins, Robert, Alan, "SDS and the Limits of Pluralism: A Test Case of The 'Rules of the Game'", 1982 (Box 1)
  - FBI file: Oglesby, Carl, 1966 (Box 1)
    Includes a summary of his work with SDS, transcripts of speeches and background information with Oglesby's annotations.
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1965 (Box 2)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1965-1968 (Box 2)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1965-1968 (Box 2)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1965-1968 (Box 3)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1965-1968 (Box 3)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1965-1969 (Box 3)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1965-1978 (Box 3)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1966 (Box 3)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1966-1968 (Box 4)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1966-1968 (Box 4)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1966-1969 (Box 4)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1967-1969 (Box 4)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1967-1969 (Box 5)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1968 (Box 5)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1968 (Box 5)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1968 (Box 5)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1968-1969 (Box 5)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1969 (Box 5)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1969 (Box 5)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1969 (Box 6)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1970-1973 (Box 6)
  - FBI files: SDS activities, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Interview: Eynon, Bret, 2000 (Box 6)
  - Interview: Oglesby, Carl, 1985; Morrison, Bob (Box 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1984-2003 (Box 6)
  - Newspaper clippings: COINTELPRO, 1976-1984 (Box 6)
  - Notes, undated (Box 6)
  - Printed material, 1982, 2001, undated (Box 6)
  - Publicity flyer for "When Students Made History!", ca. 1980; Oglesby, Carl (Box 7)
  - Speech: "Let Us Share the Future", 1965; Oglesby, Carl (Box 7)
  - Speech: "The Murder of President John Kennedy in 1963 and in 1968 of Rev. Martin Luther King and Senator Robert Kennedy", undated; Oglesby, Carl (Box 7)
  - Thesis: "Governmental Surveillance of the New Student Left in the USA and the Federal Republic of Germany in the Sixties", 1988; Schaller, Thomas Alfred (Box 7)
  - Timeline, 1969-1973 (Box 7)
  - Writing fragments, undated (Box 7)
- Series 2: JFK Assassination, 1964-2005
  - "Report to President Bush: Who Murdered John F. Kennedy?", ca. 1989; Anderson, Jack (Box 7)
  - "Day America Changed", 1983; Arisian, Khoren (Box 7)
  - "Dallas: Six Seconds That Changed History", 1983; Arisian, Khoren (Box 7)
  - Assassination Archives and Research Center, 1987-1999 (Box 7)
  - Assassination bibliography, 1975 (Box 7)
  - "Background Briefing on Santos Trafficante", circa 1975; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 7)
  - Bibliographies, circa 1975-1977; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 7)
  - Board of Directors, 1977; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 7)
  - Certificates of registration, 1975-1977; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 7)
  - Clandestine America, 1977 July-Aug; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 7)
  - Clandestine America, 1977 Sept-Oct; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 7)
  - Clandestine America, 1977 Nov-Dec; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 7)
  - Clandestine America, 1978 Jan-Feb; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 7)
  - Clandestine America, 1978 Mar-Apr; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 7)
  - Clandestine America, 1978 may-June; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 7)
  - Clandestine America, 1978 Sept-Oct; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 7)
  - Clandestine America, 1978 Nov-Dec/1979 Jan-Feb; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 7)
  - Clandestine America, 1979 Mar-Apr/May-June; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 7)
  - Clandestine America, 1979 July-Aug/Sept-Oct; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 7)
  - Clandestine America, 1979 Nov-Dec/1980 Jan-Feb; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 7)
  - Coolidge Company, Inc.Mailing list consultants. 1975-1976, Assassination Information Bureau (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1979; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, fundraising, 1977; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, speaking engagements, 1975-1976; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 8)
  - Financial records, 1978; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 8)
  - Helms, Richard McGarrah, 1978; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 8)
  - Information package index, circa 1977; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 8)
  - Information package requests, 1977; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 8)
  - Mailer, Norman, 1977; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 8)
  - Media contacts, circa 1975; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 8)
  - Newsletter memo, 1977; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 8)
  - Notes, 1975-1978; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 8)
  - Petition to Congress, circa 1976; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 8)
  - Press release and publicity, 1974-1981; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 8)
  - Printed letter, 1977 Jan 20; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 8)
  - Proposal for support, 1977 Oct 1; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 8)
  - Proposal for support, drafts, circa 1977; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 8)
  - Washington Progress Report, 1977 Jan; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 8)
  - Washington Progress Report, 1977 Feb-Mar; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 8)
  - Washington Progress Report, 1977 Apr-May; Assassination Information Bureau (Box 8)
  - Assassination Records Review Board, 1995-1998 (Box 8)
  - Book catalogue: "Political Conspiracy, and the Kennedy Family", 1997 (Box 8)
    The last Hurrah Bookshop (Williamsport, Pa.)
  - Press release, 1992; Boren, David, Senator (Box 8)
  - Castro, Fidel: essays, circa 1977, undated (Box 8)
  - Castro, Fidel: essay, circa 1977 (Box 8)
    Author's surname Wynstra.
  - Castro, Fidel: essay, "The JFK Assassinations, the Press, and the Deatth of Johnny Rosselli", circa 1977 (Box 8)
  - Newsletter, 1992 Oct; Committee for an Open Archives (Box 8)
  - Computer diskettes, 1989 (Box 9)
    Includes a CIA name file.
  - Congressional Record, 1992 (Box 9)
  - Thirty Years of Deception, circa 1993; Coogan, Matthw A. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, 1975, 1991 (Box 9)
  - Court documents, 1992-2005 (Box 9)
  - Cuban Missile Crisis: essay, "Back in the U.S.A. -- I Survive the Cuban Missile Crisis", undated (Box 9)
  - Dateline: Dallas, 1993; v. 2, no. 1 & 2 (Box 9)
  - House Select Committee on Assassinations preliminary report, 1976; Dodd, Christopher J. (Box 9)
  - Echoes of Conspiracy, 1983; v. 5, no. 4 (Box 9)
  - Fund for Constitutional Government memo, circa 1976 (Box 9)
  - "One Story of the Assassination of President John F. Kennedy", undated; Hibbard, John (Box 9)
  - Hopwood Newsletter, 1994 Dec (Box 9)
  - Remarks, 1979; House Select Committee on Assassinations (Box 9)
  - Autopsy panel review, 1968, 1978; Humes, James J., Dr. (Box 9)
  - Testimony, 1964; Humes, James J., Dr. (Box 9)
  - Institute for Media Analysis, Inc., 1988-1993 (Box 9)
  - "Howard, 'We Hardly Knew Ye,'", circa 1977; Louis, J.C. and Goldberg, Jeff (Box 10)
    Outline of book.
  - "The Reagan Administration, Organized Crime and the left", 1981; Molden, Dan (Box 9)
  - Monroe, Marilyn: postcards, 1989 (Box 9)
  - National Security Archive, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Newspaper clippings and articles, 1969-1977 (Box 9)
  - Newspaper clippings and articles, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Newspaper clippings and articles, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Newspaper clippings and articles, 1981-1983 (Box 10)
  - Newspaper clippings and articles, 1984-1988 (Box 10)
  - Newspaper clippings and articles, 1990-1994 (Box 10)
  - Newspaper clippings and articles, 1995-2003 (Box 10)
  - Newspaper clippings and articles, undated (Box 10)
  - Newspaper clippings and articles: House Select Committee on Assassinations, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Newspaper clippings and articles: House Select Committee on Assassinations, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Article, "The Second Gunman of Dealey Plaza", circa 1981; Oglesby, Carl (Box 10)
  - Article, "Too Clever by Half: How Posner Gets it Wrong", 1993; Oglesby, Carl (Box 10)
  - Article, "United States of Conspiracy", 1977; Oglesby, Carl (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, 1990; Oglesby, Carl (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, 1992; Oglesby, Carl (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, 1990; Oglesby, Carl (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, 1993 Jan-Mar; Oglesby, Carl (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, 1993 Apr; Oglesby, Carl (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, 1993 May-Nov; Oglesby, Carl (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, 1996-2005; Oglesby, Carl (Box 11)
  - Flyers and posters, 1978-1992; Oglesby, Carl (Box 11, OS)
  - Lecture, "Assassinations and the War"Assassinations Conference Keynote., 1993; Oglesby, Carl (Box 11)
  - Lecture, "JFK Assassination"Delivered at Brookline High School., 1984; Oglesby, Carl (Box 11)
  - Lecture script, 1996; Oglesby, Carl (Box 11)
  - Lecture, "Who Cares Who Killed JFK?", circa 1990; Oglesby, Carl (Box 11)
    Talking points for a public appearance.
  - Lecture, "Who Killed JFK?", 1993, undated; Oglesby, Carl (Box 11)
    Lecture notes.
  - Lecture, "Who Killed JFK?", 1980-1983; Oglesby, Carl (Box 11)
    Lecture posters.
  - Lecture, "Who Killed JFK?", undated; Oglesby, Carl (Box 11)
    Lecture references.
  - Lecture, "Who Killed JFK?", 1986-1994; Oglesby, Carl (Box 11)
    Lecture scripts.
  - Notes, 1993-1998, undated; Oglesby, Carl (Box 11)
  - Typescript, 1978; Oglesby, Carl (Box 11)
  - Typescript, 1979; Oglesby, Carl (Box 11)
  - Typescript, "Colby and the New CIA", 1973; Oglesby, Carl (Box 11)
  - Typescript, notes, 1978; Oglesby, Carl (Box 11)
  - Typescript, "Shot from the Grasy Knoll", circa 1979; Oglesby, Carl (Box 11)
  - Typescript, "Where to in JFK?", circa 1979; Oglesby, Carl (Box 11)
  - "Who Killed JFK?" book proofs, 1992; Oglesby, Carl (Box 11)
  - Oswald: The Secret Files, 1992 (Box 11)
  - People and the Pursuit of Truth, 1976; v. 2, nos. 1, 5-7. (Box 11)
  - Printed material, 1974-1977 (Box 11)
  - Assassinations, Dallas and Beyond: A Guide to Cover-Ups and Investigations, 1976; Scott, Peter Dale (Box 11)
  - Typescript, undated; Scott, Peter Dale (Box 12)
    Chapters 1-3.
  - Typescript, undated; Scott, Peter Dale (Box 12)
    Chapters 4-11.
  - War Conspiracy, book chapters, 1972; Scott, Peter Dale (Box 12)
  - "A Remembrance of President Kennedy", 1992; Sonzski, William (Box 12)
  - Special Gallery Report: The JFK Assassination, 1979 (Box 12)
  - Television program: "Who Killed Lee Harvey Oswald?", 1993 (Box 12)
  - Typescript, fragment: Minutemen, undated (Box 12)
  - Investigation of the Assassination of President John F. Kennedy: Hearings Before the Select Committee on Assassinations of the U.S. House of Representatives, Ninety-fifth Congress, Second Session, 1978-1979; United States. Congress. House Select Committee on Assassinations; v. 1-7, 9-11 (Box 13)
  - Investigation of the Assassination of Martin Luther King, Jr. :Hearings Before the Select Committee on Assassinations of the U.S. House of Representatives, Ninety-fifth Congress, Second Session, 1979; United States. Congress. House Select Committee on Assassinations; v. 1-13 (Box 14-15)
  - Contract: lecture engagements, 1975; Yazijian, Harvey (Box 12)
- Series 3: Yankee and Cowboy War, 1970-2002
  - Advertising, circa 1976 (Box 12, OS)
  - Articles, 1970-1995 (Box 12)
  - Charts, circa 1975 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, 1976-1986 (Box 12)
  - Critiques: Yankee-Cowboy theory, 1976-1996, undated (Box 12)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1972-1979 (Box 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1981-1985 (Box 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1981-1985 (Box 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1981-1985 (Box 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1985-1989 (Box 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1990-1993 (Box 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1994-2002, undated (Box 17)
  - Notes, 1974-1994 (Box 17)
  - Notes, undated (Box 17)
  - Notes: Watergate, 1982-1990 (Box 17)
    Chapter 6.
  - Notes: Yankee-Cowboy War history, circa 1973-1976 (Box 17)
  - Printed materials, 1973-2000 (Box 17)
  - Research materials: Bush administration, 1990, undated (Box 17)
  - Research materials: Carter administration, 1976-1977 (Box 17)
  - Research materials: Castro, Fidel, 1963, 1993 (Box 17)
  - Research materials: chapter 5, "1968", 1982-1990 (Box 17)
  - Research materials: chapter 6, "Watergate", 1972-1998 (Box 18)
  - Research materials: chapter 10, "Bush: One-Man Yankee-Cowboy Coalition", 1978-1990 (Box 18)
  - Research materials: chapter 10, "Bush: One-Man Yankee-Cowboy Coalition", 1978-1990 (Box 18)
  - Research materials: chapter 11, "Beyond the Frontier", 1989-1990 (Box 18)
  - Research materials: Clinton administration, 1992-1993 (Box 18)
  - Research materials: Connally, John, 1972-1993 (Box 18)
  - Research materials: Hughes, Howard, 1972-1992 (Box 18)
    Includes correspondence with Clifford Irving.
  - Research materials: introduction and afterward, 1993-1997 (Box 18)
  - Research materials: Iran-Contra, 1992 (Box 18)
  - Research materials: Kennedy, John F., 1973-1993 (Box 19)
  - Research materials: Northgate, 1981-1992 (Box 19)
  - Research materials: Northgate, 1981-1992 (Box 19)
  - Research materials: Prussians and traders, 1977 (Box 19)
  - Research materials: Reagan administration, 1990-1993 (Box 19)
  - Research materials: Watergate, 1972-1973 (Box 19)
    Letters of James McCord.
  - Research materials: Watergate, 1973-1980 (Box 19)
  - Research materials: Yankee-Cowboy War history, 1972-2003 (Box 19)
  - Review and press releases, 1976-1977 (Box 19)
  - Typescript: appendix, index, undated (Box 20)